ukti.gov.uk 2013-12-15

# Privacy and Cookies

## Data Protection Act 1998

UK Trade & Investment (UKTI) processes personal data for the purposes of promoting UK business competitiveness, to help secure overseas sales and investments and to support and develop UK inward investment. Recipients of the personal data we may hold on you may include our UK regional network, our overseas network, other UK Government Departments and our partners.

## Cookies

UKTI provides details on what [_cookies do and a full list that UKTI uses_](http://www.ukti.gov.uk/uktihome/item/142860.html) on its websites.

## Registration information

You do not have to register to use the UKTI website, but you do need to register to follow up on business opportunities and obtain access to premium content or receive updates about the site.

As a minimum we require as mandatory for you to register us with: your username (which does not need to be your real name), a password, e-mail address and your location. This information is stored securely on our database so that you do not need to re-register when you come back to the site.

You can change your registration preferences, e-mail address and login details through the website at any time. If you wish to amend your personal profile, please click on the 'Login’ link at the top of the page, log in to your account, go to ‘My Account’ and ‘Edit Account Details’, then check/uncheck the options available. If you are no longer interested in receiving UKTI email alerts click, deselect the ‘send me marketing information about UK Trade & Investment by e-mail’. Alternatively, select the ‘Unsubscribe' link at the bottom of your email alerts. 

## Feedback

You can send a message to UKTI using our [Contact us](http://www.ukti.gov.uk/uktihome/contactus/contactusform.html) form. If you are asking for information we do not already publish on the site, we will deal with your query. In doing so we may need to contact other organisations to find answers to your questions. If your question is technical, we may need to pass it to our technology supplier. In such cases we will only pass on personal data if it is necessary to do so, and we will not keep your personal data or records of our correspondence longer than necessary.

## Updating your personal information

You have the right to access and correct the personal information retained by the website. To do this, log into the website using your username and password. From the menu on the left, click ‘My Account’ and then ‘Edit Account Details’

## Changes to this Privacy and Data Protection statement

If this privacy and data protection statement changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.

If you have a query or complaint about this privacy policy or about the site, you can contact via our [_Contact Us form_](http://www.ukti.gov.uk/uktihome/contactus/contactusform.html).

## Data Controller

Any information you provide will be held securely and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

You have a right to request a copy of your personal details at any time to check the accuracy of the information held. If you want to ask whether UKTI holds any personal data relating to you, please write to us at:

Data Protection Officer

Department for Business, Innovation and Skills

Commercial Directorate/Information Rights Unit

1 Victoria Street

London 

SW1H 0ET

Alternatively you can email your request to [_dataprotection@bis.gsi.gov.uk_](mailto:dataprotection@bis.gsi.gov.uk)

We need to handle personal information about you so that we can provide services for you. This is how we look after that information. 

When we ask you for personal information, we promise:

  * to make sure you know why we need it ; 

  * to only ask for information proportionate to what we need; 

  * to protect it and make sure nobody has access to it who shouldn't; 

  * to let you know if we share it with other organisations to give you better public services - and if you can say no; 

  * to make sure we don't keep it longer than necessary; and 

  * not to make your personal information available for commercial use without your permission. 

In return, we ask you to:

  * give us accurate information; and 

  * tell us as soon as possible if there are any changes, such as a new address. 

This helps us to keep your information reliable and up to date.

You can ask for more information on:

  * how to find out what information we hold about you and how to ask us to correct any mistakes; 

  * agreements we have with other organisations for sharing information; 

  * our instructions to staff on how to collect, use and delete your personal information; 

  * how we check the information we hold is accurate and up to date; and 

  * how to make a complaint. 

For more information, please contact: 

Andrew Strachan

Email: [_andrew.strachan@ukti.gsi.gov.uk_](mailto:andrew.strachan@ukti.gsi.gov.uk)

In abiding by these commitments, we will keep to the law, including the Data Protection Act 1998 and the Freedom of Information Act 2000. For independent advice about data protection, privacy and data-sharing issues, you can contact the Information Commissioner at: 

Wycliffe House, 

Water Lane, 

Wilmslow, 

Cheshire, 

SK9 5AF. 

Phone: 08456 30 60 60 or 01625 54 57 45 

Fax: 01625 524510.

Website: [_www.ico.org.uk_](http://www.ico.org.uk/)

UK Trade & Investment May 2011
